(a) 14 commits

(b) I last modified the .gitignore file when I first created the properties and book text files on 09/16/2024 at 5:49 PM

(c) We can use the command git..???

(d) I don't have a source folder :(

(e) I also don't have a remove folder, I'm not sure if I did something wrong :(

(f) git log shows the commit history of the repository, which includes all of the information associated with each commit like the author name, date, and message. git status shows the current state of the working directory and the staging area. It displays what files have been modified, which have staged for commit, the files that aren't tracked and if the current branch is ahead or behind the remote branch.

(g) git shortlog shows a list of the commits done by each author on the repository except that it's a shortened version of the regular log where it only shows the subject or short messages left on each commit and no other information about the commits.

(h) git log -- Main.java
(i) git log --follow -p -- Main.java
(j) git log --grep="account"
(k) git log --author="AuthorNameHere"
(l) git log --author="Lauren" --since"2014-01-05" --until="2024-01-14"